A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1965
  - Education Program, 1965; 2
    - Ypsilanti Public Schools, Mich. - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1491)
  - Humanities and Arts Program (HA), 1965; 3
    - Program A - CG, 1965 (Reel C-1477)
    - CH - MN, 1965 (Reel C-1478)
    - MO - Stone, Kurt, 1965 (Reel C-1479)
    - Sym. Assoc. of Orange County - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1480)
  - International Affairs Program (IA), 1965; 4
    - A - ET, 1965 (Reel C-1496)
    - EU - N, 1965 (Reel C-1497)
    - O - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1498)
    - A -Z, 1965 (Reel C-1485)
  - Middle East and Africa Program (MEA), 1965; 5
    - A - PZ, 1965 (Reel C-1491)
    - Q - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1492)
  - Overseas Division - Latin American (OD/LA), 1965; 6
    - A - American, 1965 (Reel C-1493)
    - American - Latin America, 1965 (Reel C-1494)
    - Lowry - Saint..., 1965 (Reel C-1495)
    - Sixth Pan American Congress - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1496)
  - Population Program (POP), 1965; 7
    - A - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1484)
  - Public Affairs Program (PA), 1965; 8
    - A - CM, 1965 (Reel C-1480)
    - CO - HN, 1965 (Reel C-1481)
    - HO - PK, 1965 (Reel C-1482)
    - PL - UZ, 1965 (Reel C-1483)
    - United Nations - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1484)
  - Science & Engineering, 1965; 9
    - A - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1499)
  - South and Southeast Asia Program (SSEA), 1965; 10
    - A - India, 1965 (Reel C-1492)
    - India - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1493)
  - Vice President, Office of the (VP), 1965; 11
    - A - I, 1965 (Reel C-1498)
    - Industrial Hygiene - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1499)
- General Correspondence, 1966
  - Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA), 1966; 1
    - A - Herndon College, 1966 (Reel C-1515)
    - I - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1516)
  - Education Program, 1966; 2
    - A - California, Univ. of (Los Angeles), 1966 (Reel C-1504)
    - California, Univ. of Teaching Asst. Prog. - Garland Junior College, 1966 (Reel C-1505)
    - Great Lakes Colleges Assoc. - MI, 1966 (Reel C-1506)
    - MJ - Ohio State University, 1966 (Reel C-1507)
    - Oklahoma State Univ. - Rutgers Univ., 1966 (Reel C-1508)
    - SA -V, 1966 (Reel C-1509)
    - Valley Assn. for Sup. Education, Texas - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1510)
  - Humanities and Arts Program (HA), 1966; 3
    - A - BL, 1966 (Reel C-1510)
    - BO - LL, 1966 (Reel C-1511)
    - LO - VZ, 1966 (Reel C-1512)
    - W - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1513)
  - International Relations (IR), 1966; 4
    - A - Comm. Of Corr., 1966 (Reel C-1518)
    - Comm. For Economic Dev. - Foreign Policy Institute, 1966 (Reel C-1519)
    - GA - Opera Mundi Europe, 1966 (Reel C-1520)
    - PA - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1521)
  - International Training and Research (ITR), 1966; 5
    - A - Mississippi State Univ., 1966 (Reel C-1514)
    - Monhonk Trust - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1515)
  - National Affairs (NA), 1966; 6
    - A - CE, 1966 (Reel C-1500)
    - CF - FZ, 1966 (Reel C-1501)
    - Five Towns Community House - Michigan, Univ. of, 1966 (Reel C-1502)
    - Mueller, G.O - Southern Consumers.., 1966 (Reel C-1503)
    - Southwest Legal Foundation - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1504)
  - Overseas Division, 1966; 7
    - A - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1521)
  - Overseas Division - Latin American and the Caribbean (OD/LAC), 1966; 8
    - A - AG, 1966 (Reel C-1521)
    - Agency for International Dev. - Educational & World Affairs, 1966 (Reel C-1522)
    - Educational & World Affairs - L, 1966 (Reel C-1523)
    - Latin America, Jan. - Overseas Development Institute, 1966 (Reel C-1524)
    - P - V, 1966 (Reel C-1525)
    - Venezuela: Caracas Field Office - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1526)
  - Overseas Division - Middle East and Africa (OD/MEA), 1966; 9
    - A - Fough, Mrs. Adel, 1966 (Reel C-1526)
    - Franklin Book Programs - UZ, 1966 (Reel C-1527)
    - United Arab Republic - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1528)
  - Overseas Division - South and Southeast Asia (OD/SSEA), 1966; 10
    - A - India, 1966 (Reel C-1528)
    - India Cultural Prop. - Sangam Planning Comm., 1966 (Reel C-1529)
    - Santa Clara, Univ. of - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1530)
  - Population Program (POP), 1966; 11
    - A - B, 1966 (Reel C-1516)
    - Beshers, J. - P, 1966 (Reel C-1517)
    - Pan American Health Organization - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1518)
  - Research & Education Program (R&E), 1966; 12
    - All R&E correspondence for 1966 - 1970 is filed under the year 1970
    - A - COR, 1967 (Reel C-1580)
    - COS - HAV, 1967 (Reel C-1581)
    - HAW - National, 1967 (Reel C-1582)
    - National - St. John's College, 1967 (Reel C-1583)
    - Stanford Univ. - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1584)
  - Science & Engineering, 1966; 13
    - A - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1510)
  - Vice President, Office of the (VP), 1966; 14
    - A - Bundy, McGeorge, 1966 (Reel C-1530)
    - C - Harvard Univ., 1966 (Reel C-1531)
    - IA - New Mexico State Hosp., 1966 (Reel C-1532)
    - New School - Z, 1966 (Reel C-1533)
- General Correspondence, 1967
  - Higher Education and Research (HER), 1967; 1
    - A - Berry College, 1967 (Reel C-1522)
    - C - Friends World Institute, 1967 (Reel C-1553)
    - G - Missouri, Univ. of, at Kansas City, 1967 (Reel C-1554)
    - Montor, Karel - RAND Corp., 1967 (Reel C-1555)
    - S - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1556)
  - Humanities and Arts Program (HA), 1967; 2
    - A - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, School of, 1967 (Reel C-1557)
    - C - F, 1967 (Reel C-1558)
    - G - M, 1967 (Reel C-1559)
    - N - Regional, 1967 (Reel C-1560)
    - Rossi - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1561)
  - International Relations, Office of (OIR), 1967; 3
    - A - Canellas, 1967 (Reel C-1564)
    - Carnegie - International, 1967 (Reel C-1565)
    - International - Oak Ridge, 1967 (Reel C-1566)
    - P - UNESCO, 1967 (Reel C-1567)
    - United Nations Social Defense - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1568)
  - Latin America and Caribbean Program (LAC), 1967; 4
    - A - Brazil, 1967 (Reel C-1568)
    - G - Di Tella Inst., 1967 (Reel C-1569)
    - E - Inter-American, 1967 (Reel C-1570)
    - Inter-American - Latin American Admin., 1967 (Reel C-1571)
    - Latin American Admin. - Pan American Health Org, 1967 (Reel C-1572)
    - Pan American Health Org - Stanford Univ., 1967 (Reel C-1573)
    - T - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1574)
  - Middle East and Africa Program (MEA), 1967; 5
    - A - B, 1967 (Reel C-1574)
    - C - M, 1967 (Reel C-1575)
    - N - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1576)
  - National Affairs Program (NA), 1967; 6
    - A - California, 1967 (Reel C-1534)
    - California Center for Community Dev. - Elson, Alex, 1967 (Reel C-1535)
    - FA - Housing Opportunity Made Equal, 1967 (Reel C-1536)
    - IA - Lacy, Frank, 1967 (Reel C-1537)
    - Lanning, Geoffrey - NZ, 1967 (Reel C-1538)
    - National - PERI, 1967 (Reel C-1539)
    - Perry - S, 1967 (Reel C-1540)
    - Saint - United, 1967 (Reel C-1541)
    - Urban - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1542)
  - Population (POP), 1967; 7
    - A - Iran, 1967 (Reel C-1562)
    - J - S, 1967 (Reel C-1563)
    - T - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1564)
  - Public Education (PE), 1967; 8
    - A - Academy of the Sacred Heart (Cinn. Ohio), 1967 (Reel C-1542)
    - American - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1967 (Reel C-1543)
    - Center for Research in Careers - Daedalus, 1967 (Reel C-1544)
    - Delaware Tutorial & Job - Hartford Public Schools, 1967 (Reel C-1545)
    - Harvard Univ. - Louisburg College, 1967 (Reel C-1546)
    - MA - N, 1967 (Reel C-1547)
    - National - Potomac School, 1967 (Reel C-1548)
    - Potash - Spencer, John, 1967 (Reel C-1549)
    - Springdale Para-Psychiatric- Technical Education, 1967 (Reel C-1550)
    - Texas A&M Univ. - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1551)
  - Research & Education Program (R&E), 1967; 9
    - All R&E correspondence for 1966 - 1970 is filed under the year 1970, 1967
  - Science and Technology, 1967; 10
    - A- Z, 1967 (Reel C-1584)
  - South and Southeast Asia Program (SSEA), 1967; 11
    - A - Beers, Howard, 1967 (Reel C-1576)
    - Bernitez, H. - Higher Educ. & Development in Southeast Asia, 1967 (Reel C-1577)
    - I - Pakistan, 1967 (Reel C-1578)
    - Pakistan - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1579)
  - Vice President, Office of the (VP), 1967; 12
    - A - COR, 1967 (Reel C-1580)
    - COS - HAV, 1967 (Reel C-1581)
    - HAW - National, 1967 (Reel C-1582)
    - National - St. John's College, 1967 (Reel C-1583)
    - Stanford Univ. - Z, 1967 (Reel C-1584)
- General Correspondence, 1968
  - Asia and Pacific Program (A&P), 1968; 1
    - A - Center for Rural Dev., 1968 (Reel C-1597)
    - Centre for Curriculum & Educ. Dev. - Indonesia, 1968 (Reel C-1598)
    - Inst. Of International Education - R, 1968 (Reel C-1599)
    - S - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1600)
  - European and International Affairs (EIA), 1968; 2
    - A - Boy Scouts, 1968 (Reel C-1594)
    - C - M, 1968 (Reel C-1595)
    - N - University College Dublin, 1968 (Reel C-1596)
    - V - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1597)
  - Higher Education and Research (HER), 1968; 3
    - A - American., 1968 (Reel C-1622)
    - American - D, 1968 (Reel C-1623)
    - E - Inst. Of International Education, 1968 (Reel C-1624)
    - J - National, 1968 (Reel C-1625)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Rossman, 1968 (Reel C-1626)
    - S - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1627)
    - Survey of Black Americans in Higher Education, 1968 (Reel C-1628)
  - Humanities and Arts (HA), 1968; 4
    - A - American Assembly, 1968 (Reel C-1607)
    - B - F, 1968 (Reel C-1608)
    - G - L, 1968 (Reel C-1609)
    - M - P, 1968 (Reel C-1610)
    - Q - T, 1968 (Reel C-1611)
    - Texas, Univ. of - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1612)
  - Latin America and Caribbean Program (LAC), 1968; 5
    - A - Agribusiness Council, 1968 (Reel C-1600)
    - American - D, 1968 (Reel C-1601)
    - DiTella Inst. - International Development Foundation, 1968 (Reel C-1602)
    - Israel - National, 1968 (Reel C-1603)
    - National Academy of Sciences - U, 1968 (Reel C-1604)
    - Utah State Univ. - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1605)
  - Middle East and Africa Program (MEA), 1968; 6
    - A - Education of Angolan Refugees, 1968 (Reel C-1605)
    - Ethiopia - Pittsburgh, Univ. of, 1968 (Reel C-1606)
    - R - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1607)
  - National Affairs Program (NA), 1968; 7
    - A - Arctic Inst. Of America, 1968 (Reel C-1629)
    - Arizona State University - B, 1968 (Reel C-1630)
    - Beaufort, North Carolina - C, 1968 (Reel C-1631)
    - California rural Legal Assistance - Churchill, 1968 (Reel C-1632)
    - Commerce & Industry Association - Drury, 1968 (Reel C-1633)
    - Duck - Friedmann, 1968 (Reel C-1634)
    - Friedlander - G, 1968 (Reel C-1635)
    - Gamaliel Foundation - H, 1968 (Reel C-1636)
    - Harvard Univ. - Job Loan, 1968 (Reel C-1637)
    - Job Resources - L, 1968 (Reel C-1638)
    - Lincoln Hospital - M, 1968 (Reel C-1639)
    - M - Nel, 1968 (Reel C-1640)
    - Nersica - New York, 1968 (Reel C-1641)
    - New York State Narcotics Add. - Portuondo, 1968 (Reel C-1642)
    - Potomac - Q, 1968 (Reel C-1643)
    - R - Santoro, 1968 (Reel C-1644)
    - Sassenberg - St. Leonard's House, 1968 (Reel C-1645)
    - Salk Institute - Streets, Virgus, 1968 (Reel C-1646)
    - T - Urban League of Westchester, 1968 (Reel C-1647)
    - Urban Planning Aids - Wiesemann, 1968 (Reel C-1648)
    - Wiley - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1649)
    - PLANNING A-Z, 1968 (Reel C-1649)
  - Population Program (POP), 1968; 8
    - A - L, 1968 (Reel C-1593)
      Includes correspondence with Dr. Katherine Kuder, consultant in family planning, re: request for sample of Goldstein Ring intrauterine device (IUD), filed under "K".
    - M - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1594)
  - Public Education (PE), 1968; 9
    - A - American, 1968 (Reel C-1612)
    - American Inst. For Research - Cleveland, 1968 (Reel C-1613)
    - Coalition - D, 1968 (Reel C-1614)
    - Day Care Council of New York - F, 1968 (Reel C-1615)
    - G - Harvard Univ., 1968 (Reel C-1616)
    - Human Resources Admin. - L, 1968 (Reel C-1617)
    - M - National, 1968 (Reel C-1618)
    - National Assn. for Educ. Of Young Children - P, 1968 (Reel C-1619)
    - Pennsylvania - S, 1968 (Reel C-1620)
    - Saginaw Public Schools - T, 1968 (Reel C-1621)
    - Tamalpais Union High School - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1622)
  - Research & Education Program (R&E), 1968; 10
    - All R&E correspondence for 1966 - 1970 is filed under the year 1970, 1968
  - Vice President, Office of the (VP), 1968; 11
    - A - American, 1968 (Reel C-1585)
    - Association - CA, 1968 (Reel C-1586)
    - California Ints. Of Tech. - Essays on Civil..., 1968 (Reel C-1587)
    - F - International, 1968 (Reel C-1588)
    - International Bank - M, 1968 (Reel C-1589)
    - Mc / MaC - Q, 1968 (Reel C-1590)
    - R - S, 1968 (Reel C-1591)
    - Saint - World, 1968 (Reel C-1592)
    - World Peace Foundation - Z, 1968 (Reel C-1593)
- General Correspondence, 1969
  - Asia and Pacific Program (A&P), 1969; 1
    - A - H, 1969 (Reel C-1659)
    - I - MZ, 1969 (Reel C-1660)
    - Malaysia - S, 1969 (Reel C-1661)
    - T - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1662)
  - European and International Affairs (EIA), 1969; 2
    - A - I, 1969 (Reel C-1663)
    - J - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1664)
  - Higher Education & Research Program (HER), 1969; 3
    - A - BD, 1969 (Reel C-1680)
      Includes Public Education (PE) correspondence for 1969
    - BE - BZ, 1969 (Reel C-1681)
    - C - COL, 1969 (Reel C-1682)
    - COM - California, 1969 (Reel C-1683)
    - California, Univ. of - DI, 1969 (Reel C-1684)
    - DO - FOS, 1969 (Reel C-1685)
    - FOT - HOO, 1969 (Reel C-1686)
    - HOR - KEL, 1969 (Reel C-1687)
    - KEN - MA, 1969 (Reel C-1688)
    - ME - MZ, 1969 (Reel C-1689)
    - N - National, 1969 (Reel C-1690)
    - New York - PEO, 1969 (Reel C-1691)
    - PER - RI, 1969 (Reel C-1692)
    - RO - SIE, 1969 (Reel C-1693)
    - SIL - SW, 1969 (Reel C-1694)
    - SY - US, 1969 (Reel C-1695)
    - UT - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1696)
  - Humanities & Arts Program (HA), 1969; 4
    - A - B, 1969 (Reel C-1674)
    - C - EK, 1969 (Reel C-1675)
    - EL - KN, 1969 (Reel C-1676)
    - KO - N, 1969 (Reel C-1677)
    - O - SP, 1969 (Reel C-1678)
    - ST - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1679)
  - Latin America and Caribbean Program (LAC), 1969; 5
    - A - BZ, 1969 (Reel C-1665)
    - Bolivia - C, 1969 (Reel C-1666)
    - D - Inter-American, 1969 (Reel C-1667)
    - Inter-American Center of Tax Admin - NZ, 1969 (Reel C-1668)
    - National - RZ, 1969 (Reel C-1669)
    - Rejection - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1670)
  - Middle East and Africa Program (MEA), 1969; 6
    - A - E, 1969 (Reel C-1656)
    - F - R, 1969 (Reel C-1657)
    - S - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1658)
  - National Affairs Program (NA), 1969; 7
    - A - Afro Urban Inst., 1969 (Reel C-1709)
    - AFL-CIO - BEE, 1969 (Reel C-1710)
    - BEI - Black American, 1969 (Reel C-1711)
    - Black Inc. - CE, 1969 (Reel C-1712)
    - CH - Cooperative, 1969 (Reel C-1713)
    - Cooperative - Colorado, 1969 (Reel C-1714)
    - Columbia University - Community for Awareness, 1969 (Reel C-1715)
    - Community Justice - DZ, 1969 (Reel C-1716)
    - Denver, Univ. of - Federal, 1969 (Reel C-1717)
    - Federation - FZ, 1969 (Reel C-1718)
    - G - HARL, 1969 (Reel C-1719)
    - HARP - HZ, 1969 (Reel C-1720)
    - I - Institute of Urban Studies (Univ. of Texas), 1969 (Reel C-1721)
    - International - K, 1969 (Reel C-1722)
    - LA - MARG, 1969 (Reel C-1723)
    - MARI - MI, 1969 (Reel C-1724)
    - MO - Mobilization for Urban Action, 1969 (Reel C-1725)
    - Mosely - NZ, 1969 (Reel C-1726)
    - National - National Study Service, 1969 (Reel C-1727)
    - Neighborhood Consumer Information Center - New Haven, 1969 (Reel C-1728)
    - New School for Social Research - PK, 1969 (Reel C-1729)
    - PL - REI, 1969 (Reel C-1730)
    - REN - SAC, 1969 (Reel C-1731)
    - SAD - STAO, 1969 (Reel C-1732)
    - STAP - San Francisco Economic, 1969 (Reel C-1733)
    - Southern Elections - Tufts Univ., 1969 (Reel C-1734)
    - Tuskegee National Alumni - Virginia State College, 1969 (Reel C-1735)
    - Virginia Union Univ. - Western Center on Law., 1969 (Reel C-1736)
    - Wisconsin, Univ. of - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1737)
  - Population Program (POP), 1969; 8
    - A - J, 1969 (Reel C-1671)
    - K - T, 1969 (Reel C-1672)
    - U - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1673)
  - Public Education Program (PE), 1969; 9
    - Included with Higher Education & Research (HER) correspondence for 1969
  - Research & Education Program (R&E), 1969; 10
    - All R&E correspondence for 1966 - 1970 is filed under the year 1970, 1969
  - Special Projects (SP), 1969; 11
    - Afro-American Studies A - S, 1969 (Reel C-1697)
    - Afro-American Studies T - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1698)
    - Central Michigan University, 1969 (Reel C-1699)
    - Central State College - DZ, 1969 (Reel C-1701)
    - E - H, 1969 (Reel C-1700)
    - Hampton Institute - L, 1969 (Reel C-1702)
    - M - National Achievement Scholarship, 1969 (Reel C-1703)
    - National Association of Colleges - Negro Students in White Univ., 1969 (Reel C-1704)
    - Negro Students in White Inst - Q, 1969 (Reel C-1705)
    - R - Spelman College, 1969 (Reel C-1706)
    - SPI - Unites States Dept. of Commerce, 1969 (Reel C-1707)
    - United States Student Press Association - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1708)
  - Vice President, Office of the (VP), 1969; 12
    - A - C, 1969 (Reel C-1650)
    - D - H, 1969 (Reel C-1651)
    - I - MA, 1969 (Reel C-1652)
    - ME - SI, 1969 (Reel C-1653)
    - SK - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1654)
    - A - Z, 1969 (Reel C-1655)
- General Correspondence, 1970
  - Asia and Pacific Program (A&P), 1970; 1
    - AA - AZ, 1970 (Reel C-1797)
    - B - CZ, 1970 (Reel C-1798)
    - Cambodia - FZ, 1970 (Reel C-1799)
    - Ford - Inter-American Canter of Tax., 1970 (Reel C-1800)
    - IA – IZ [General File]: IA – Inter-American Confederation of Chemical Engineers) -- Kats, Ivan, 1970 (Reel C-1801)
      Includes correspondence with Dr. Katherine Kuder re: training program for operative culdoscopy at Mt. Sinai Medical Center in New York (filed under "INDIA").
    - Korea - New York, State Univ. of, 1970 (Reel C-1802)
    - New York, State Univ. of, at Buffalo - Pakistan, 1970 (Reel C-1803)
    - Peru - Southern Methodist University, 1970 (Reel C-1804)
    - Southwest Research Inst. - WZ, 1970 (Reel C-1805)
    - Wisconsin - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1806)
  - European and International Affairs (EIA), 1970; 2
    - A - Bergman, 1970 (Reel C-1742)
    - Bernstein - Handler, 1970 (Reel C-1743)
    - Handry - Mantel, 1970 (Reel C-1744)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust - P, 1970 (Reel C-1745)
    - Q - West Africa, 1970 (Reel C-1746)
    - West, James - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1747)
  - Higher Education & Research (HER) and Public Education (PE), 1970; 3
    - A - Boston, 1970 (Reel C-1751)
    - Boston College - Cuetara, 1970 (Reel C-1752)
    - Cullister Foundation - Douglass House, 1970 (Reel C-1753)
    - Downey - Gonzaga Univ., 1970 (Reel C-1754)
    - Gonzalez - I, 1970 (Reel C-1755)
    - J - Michigan State Univ., 1970 (Reel C-1756)
    - Madison College - Newman, B, 1970 (Reel C-1757)
    - Newman, T - New York State Univ., 1970 (Reel C-1758)
    - New York Univ. - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1970 (Reel C-1759)
    - Pittsburgh Univ. - Rogers, 1970 (Reel C-1760)
    - Rodman - S, 1970 (Reel C-1761)
    - Saint - Toronto, Univ. of Ontario, 1970 (Reel C-1762)
    - Toronto, Univ. of - Wilmington City Schools, 1970 (Reel C-1763)
    - Wilmington College - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1764)
  - Humanities & Arts Program (HA), 1970; 4
    - A - Dildine, 1970 (Reel C-1738)
    - DC Black Repertory - LeBlanc, 1970 (Reel C-1739)
    - Lederman - Ontario Institute, 1970 (Reel C-1740)
    - Opera America Inc. - Stavitsky, 1970 (Reel C-1741)
    - Steinbach - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1742)
  - Latin America and Caribbean Program (LAC), 1970; 5
    - Filed with Asia and Pacific Program correspondence for 1970
  - Middle East and Africa Program (MEA), 1970; 6
    - A - Bergman, 1970 (Reel C-1742)
    - Bernstein - Handler, 1970 (Reel C-1743)
    - Handry - Mantel, 1970 (Reel C-1744)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust - P, 1970 (Reel C-1745)
    - Q - West Africa, 1970 (Reel C-1746)
    - West, James - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1747)
  - National Affairs Program (NA), 1970; 7
    - A - Adams State College, 1970 (Reel C-1766)
    - Adams-Morgan Federation - American Friends Service Committee, 1970 (Reel C-1767)
    - American Health Systems Inc. - Bronx Community College, 1970 (Reel C-1768)
    - Bronx State Hospital - Center for the Study of, 1970 (Reel C-1769)
    - Center for Venture Management - Ca-Cz, 1970 (Reel C-1770)
    - Calgary, Univ. of - C, 1970 (Reel C-1771)
    - D - E, 1970 (Reel C-1772)
    - F - Georgia, Univ. of, 1970 (Reel C-1773)
    - Gerhardt - Hiwassee Community Council, 1970 (Reel C-1774)
    - Hoberman - Interfaith Committee for Human Concerns, 1970 (Reel C-1775)
    - Interfaith Council for Action Inc. - Kinder Craft, Inc., 1970 (Reel C-1776)
    - King - Martinez, 1970 (Reel C-1777)
    - Mary College - Model Economic Opportunity Foundation, 1970 (Reel C-1778)
    - Model Urban Neighborhood - Northwest Baltimore Corp., 1970 (Reel C-1779)
    - Northwest Community Organization - National Industrial Mission, 1970 (Reel C-1780)
    - National Initiative Foundation - Ohios Key Appalachian, 1970 (Reel C-1781)
    - Ohio Leadership - Planned Parenthood, 1970 (Reel C-1782)
    - Planners for Equal Opportunity - Reitman, 1970 (Reel C-1783)
    - Rennsselaer Polytechnic Inst. - Seattle, City of, 1970 (Reel C-1784)
    - Seattle First National Bank - Saint, 1970 (Reel C-1785)
    - Ship-Shape Development - TZ, 1970 (Reel C-1786)
    - U - Washington State Research Council, 1970 (Reel C-1787)
    - Washington State Council of Churches - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1788)
  - Population Program (POP), 1970; 8
    - A - Bergman, 1970 (Reel C-1742)
    - Bernstein - Handler, 1970 (Reel C-1743)
    - Handry - Mantel, 1970 (Reel C-1744)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust - P, 1970 (Reel C-1745)
    - Q - West Africa, 1970 (Reel C-1746)
    - West, James - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1747)
  - Public Broadcasting Program (PB), 1970; 9
    - A - Cable Television, 1970 (Reel C-1764)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting - N, 1970 (Reel C-1765)
    - National Laboratory of Urban Communication - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1766)
  - Research & Education Program (R&E), 1970; 10
    - A - California Colleges, 1970; (Includes all R&E correspondence for 1966-1970) (Reel C-1789)
    - California Tomorrow - G, 1970; (Includes all R&E correspondence for 1966-1970) (Reel C-1790)
    - H - Miller, Daniel, 1970; (Includes all R&E correspondence for 1966-1970) (Reel C-1791)
    - Miller, Richard - R, 1970; (Includes all R&E correspondence for 1966-1970) (Reel C-1792)
    - S - Z, 1970; (Includes all R&E correspondence for 1966-1970) (Reel C-1793)
  - Special Projects (SP), 1970; 11
    - A - Central State Univ., 1970 (Reel C-1794)
    - Central YMCA Community Colleges - Minorities, Misc, A-Z, 1970 (Reel C-1795)
    - Minorities, American Indians - R, 1970 (Reel C-1796)
    - S - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1797)
  - Vice President / Executive Offices (VP), 1970; 12
    - A - Clough, 1970 (Reel C-1747)
    - Coady - International Society, 1970 (Reel C-1748)
    - International Statistical - Q, 1970 (Reel C-1749)
    - R - Z, 1970 (Reel C-1750)